aramajapan.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy | J-pop and Japanese Entertainment News

Your privacy is critically important to us. At ARAMA! JAPAN we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, ARAMA! JAPAN collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ARAMA! JAPAN’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ARAMA! JAPAN’s visitors use its website. From time to time, ARAMA! JAPAN may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

ARAMA! JAPAN also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on ARAMA! JAPAN properties. ARAMA! JAPAN only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to ARAMA! JAPAN’s websites choose to interact with ARAMA! JAPAN in ways that require ARAMA! JAPAN to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ARAMA! JAPAN gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. ARAMA! JAPAN collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with ARAMA! JAPAN. ARAMA! JAPAN does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

ARAMA! JAPAN collects statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. ARAMA! JAPAN may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ARAMA! JAPAN does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

ARAMA! JAPAN discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ARAMA! JAPAN’s behalf or to provide services available at ARAMA! JAPAN’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ARAMA! JAPAN’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. ARAMA! JAPAN will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ARAMA! JAPAN discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when ARAMA! JAPAN believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ARAMA! JAPAN, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an ARAMA! JAPAN website and have supplied your email address, ARAMA! JAPAN may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with ARAMA! JAPAN and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. ARAMA! JAPAN takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ARAMA! JAPAN uses cookies to help ARAMA! JAPAN identify and track visitors, their usage of ARAMA! JAPAN website, and their website access preferences. ARAMA! JAPAN visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ARAMA! JAPAN’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of ARAMA! JAPAN’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If ARAMA! JAPAN, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that ARAMA! JAPAN goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of ARAMA! JAPAN may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ARAMA! JAPAN and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ARAMA! JAPAN may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ARAMA! JAPAN’s sole discretion. ARAMA! JAPAN encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.
